<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Wizards Encounters</string>
    <string name="dbnamestring">WizardsEncounters.db</string>
    <string name="dbversion">1</string>
    <string name="version">V 2025 0.911</string>
    <string name="endgametext">Congratulations! You have completed all of the Rounds in this Version of Wizards Encounters. The items earned by this character are added to your Inventory, he has leveled up, and is set back to Round 1. Remember, each class has unique equipment, attacks, and abilities!</string>
   
    <string name="abilitiesHelpText">This screen is used to specify which abilities this character will enter combat with. Below, you see a list of owned Ability Runes.  These are abilities that you can equip on the currently selected character. To equip a rune, click on it and it will be added to the equipped list. You may unequip an active rune in the same way.  Each character may have a maxumum of 8 runes equipped at any time.</string>
    <string name="selectclassHelpText">On this screen you will select the Class for your new player. Each class is part of a class group.  These groups all have unique abilities, weapons, and armor they may use, and they also regenerate AP in different ways. Once you have highlighted the Class you want, press Done to go back to the new character screen.</string>
    <string name="equipweaponHelpText">To equip a new weapon, select the one you want from the list of owned weapons at the bottom. This will move it into the &quot;New&quot; box on the upper right. If you like the stats you see, click the &quot;New&quot; box and the new weapon will become equipped. When finished, press Done.</string>
    <string name="equiparmorHelpText">To equip a new piece of armor, select the one you want from the list of owned armor at the bottom. This will move it into the &quot;New&quot; box on the upper right. If you like the stats you see, click the &quot;New&quot; box and the new armor will become equipped. When finished, press Done. Some armor grants a rune if it is equipped. To be sure this rune is equipped in combat, click on the Runes button from the main inventory screen. When you unequip a piece of armor that granted a rune, that rune will be removed from your inventory.</string>
    <string name="equipitemHelpText">To equip an item, select the one you want from the list of owned items at the bottom. Be sure that it has charges remaining, or else it will be unusable during combat. To recharge your items, you must go to the store. Some items recharge automatically at the end of a fight. When you select an item from the list, it will appear in the &quot;New&quot; box on the upper right. If you want to replace your current item slot with this one, press the &quot;New&quot; box, and the old item will return to your owned items list.</string>
    <string name="inventoryHelpText">This screen shows your character\'s equipped items. The green box is your weapon slot, blue are armor slots, orange for trinket, and brown for items. The stats on the bottom will change depending on what you have equipped.  You have 3 armor slots: Helm, Chest, Shoes. Tap on any of these boxes to equip something from your owned items. The top green bar shows your current modifiers in Execution, Reaction, Knowledge, Magelore, and Luck.  These values will affect abilities and other stats during combat.  Be sure to equip your active Ability Runes by pressing the "Runes" button at the top.  Once combat starts, you cannot alter your character\'s equipment, unless you exit combat by forfeit, or complete a full round.</string>
    <string name="mainmenuHelpText">This screen shows a list of your created characters and owned Gold. You may create a new character and purchase more gold.  You do not need to purchase gold to complete the game - every moster and boss drops enough gold to purchase everything in the store. However, if you can\'t wait to play through or save up, you may purchase 1000 Gold for $1. After you create a new character, it will appear in the list below. Select who you wish to play with, and the buttons on the bottom of the screen will unlock. You should go to the Equip screen before starting a round, to make sure your selected character has all of the items and abilities you want him to have. The Store button opens up an in game store where you can spend the gold you\'ve earned on various items, as well as sell any looted items you don\'t want.  </string>

</resources>